#### **COVER LETTER**

#### Mohammad Elias Hamidi

+ 12th District, Ahmad shah Baba Mena, Kabul-Afghanistan

+93 767280458

Eliashamidi8@gmail.com

# Dear Ms. /Ms.

I am writing to express my interest in the position advertised recently by your esteemed organization. I learned about your organization from social media, after properly visiting your website and research I realized that your specifications match my skills and interest remarkably.

I did a bachelor of Computer Science and Technology from China-2023. While I have a comprehensive knowledge of computer software and hardware (IT), my main focus points are, Data Collection, Data Analyzing, Data Entry, Data Filtering, Data Visualization, IT, Web Front-End Design and Python OOP.

Previously I completed a one year contract with a Non-Governmental Organization ODSSA as IT Assistant, for more than a year. I was an active member of the IT Team. Beside that I have a 4 weeks training certificate in hacking & information security.

I always like to accept challenges, definitely this position will boost my skills and career.

Based on the position requirements I have good communication, Management, Dealing and Leadership Skills,

My language Skills are as below:

Pashto, Dari, English, Chinese, Urdu, Hindi

Your specifications match my skills and interest; I would like the opportunity to meet with you and discuss the job position, and please let me know if you have any questions you can reach me by phone at +93767280458, or by email at eliashamidi8@gmail.com.

Thank you for your consideration!

# MOHAMMAD ELIAS HAMIDI

# Lecturer

Ahmad Shah Baba Mena Kabul-Afghanistan +93 767280458 eliashamidi8@gmail.com

# **SKILLS**

<ul> <li>Data Management</li> </ul>	
<ul> <li>Data Analysis &amp; Visualization</li> </ul>	
<ul> <li>Computer General Skills</li> </ul>	
<ul><li>SuerveyCTO</li></ul>	
Data Entry	
Microsoft Office	
• Programming (HTML, CSS, JS, SQL, Python[numpy, pandas, matplotlib,	
tkinter])	
Kobo ToobBox	

# **EXPERIENCE**

SEP 2023 - Current

**Online Technology Content Creator** 

Ulearna - Kabul

- Recorded a complete python course
- Created content for website and online publication

FEB 2023 - AUG 2023

Lecturer

Jahan University - Kabul

As a lecturer I was teaching the following courses:

- C++ Programming
- Database SQL

**MAR 2017 - JAN 2018** 

**IT Assistant** 

**ODSSA NGO - Kabul** 

- Reviewed system and network performance to make proactive adjustments based on established IT policies.
- Installed and configured software and hardware.
- Monitored system performance to identify potential issues.
- Researched and identified solutions to technical problems.
- Assisted in development of system security protocols.
- Configured hardware, devices, and software to set up work stations for employees.

## **EDUCATION**

#### MAR 2019 - JAN 2023

**Bachelor of Computer Science & Technology** 

**Shenyang University of Chemical Technology - CHINA** 

- Member of student union
- CGPA 3.6/4.0

#### 2019

## **High School**

# Ghulam Sediq Muhibi High School - Afghanistan

- Elected Captain of Batch
- 3 Years overall percentage 94%

#### 2017 - 2018

**English Language Diploma'** 

# **Muslim English Language Institute**

- English A\*
- Writing, Reading, Speaking, Listening

## **LANGUAGES**

Pashto / Native	
Dari / Native	
English / Excellent	
Chinese / Basic	
Urdu / <b>Excellent</b>	

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Hack & Information Security
- IT Assistant

# **REFERENCE**

Available upon request